<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<ModMetaData>
  <name>RimCuisine 2 Meals and Munchies Expansion (Continued)</name>
  <author>Crustypeanut</author>
  <packageId>Crustypeanut.RC2.MaME</packageId>
  <supportedVersions>
    <li>1.0</li>
    <li>1.1</li>
    <li>1.2</li>
  </supportedVersions>
  <modDependencies>
    <li>
      <packageId>Crustypeanut.RC2.Core</packageId>
      <displayName>RimCuisine 2 Core</displayName>
      <steamWorkshopUrl>steam://url/CommunityFilePage/1833592062</steamWorkshopUrl>
    </li>
  </modDependencies>
  <loadAfter>
    <li>Crustypeanut.RC2.Core</li>
  </loadAfter>
  <description>Update of Crustypeanuts mod for RimWorld 1.1
https://steamcommunity.com/sharedfiles/filedetails/?id=1833592940

[img]https://i.imgur.com/GYswkZ7.png[/img]

Support-chat:
https://invite.gg/mlie

Non-steam version:
https://github.com/emipa606/RimCuisine2MealsandMunchiesExpansion
	
--- Original Description ---
RimCuisine 2: Meals and Munchies Expansion for 1.0

Welcome to RimCuisine 2: Meals and Munchies! This expansion mod is focused on expanding your colony’s repertoire of snacks, foods, and meals for your pawns to gorge themselves on!

------------------------------------------------------------

New Snacks: New snacks including crisps (chips), cupcakes, and icecream for your pawns to delight themselves on!

New Meals: Make primitive nutrient paste in the form of Rubaboo or revel in gluttonous excess with the Extravagant Meal!

New Food Preservation: Make ingredients last basically forever by canning them! Canned meat, canned vegetables, canned fruit, and canned meals can be made at a cannery! Canneries require electricity and use steel as a fuel source. Canned goods are not only a great way to preserve and store food (being 5x as compact as raw ingredients and last forever), but also are a good trading commodity! Everyone loves canned goods!

The Rim-Co Cook-o-Matic 9,000,000,000 XXXL: This high-tech piece of machinery, made from spacer components, plasteel, and a lot of love is your colony’s solution to.. Well, anything food related. Despite being a power hog at 800 W, this machine lets you produce just about any food en masse. Mass produced meals, ingredients, snacks, and drinks! Requires less skill to make stuff than a regular stove, plus saves time! The Cook-o-Matic requires both Advanced Cooking and the Fabrication techs to make, plus plasteel and spacer components (subject to balancing in time).

--------------------------------------------------

Like my mods? Consider supporting me with delicious caffeine![ko-fi.com]

--------------------------------------------------

To-do List:

Work on balance!
Minor art tweaks and fixes.
Bugfixes (hopefully there aren’t any!)
Compatibility patches!
More snacks?!?! We’ll see!

--------------------------------------------------

Compatibilities:

Same compatibilities as RimCuisine 2! Go read my rant over there! ;)</description>
</ModMetaData>